iafrica.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy - iAfrica.com

iAfrica is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of those who use iafrica.com.

Contact us by sending an email to  **iafrica @ africa.com**

###  This statement outlines how we handle any personal information we obtain.

From time to time, we may ask for data that identifies you, as in user surveys or orders placed through our site. We use this information to operate this site, provide you with the highest quality services and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest.

You also may choose to provide information about yourself by participating in various forums we intend to offer for readers. You should remember that when you yourself voluntarily disclose personal information to other Internet users, such as when you include personal information in a posting to an online discussion forum, that information could be used by others and may result in unsolicited messages or other forms of attention.

iAfrica.com uses IP addresses to analyze traffic and administer this site. IP addresses track individual computers and do not contain personally identifiable data. In order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and others, we may disclose user information, but only in a form that does not identify individuals. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are female or within a certain age range.

## E-Commerce

When iafrica.com offers items for sale, information is collected to process the orders and is used only in relation to that transaction. It is not sold to other vendors. We also host or provide links to advertisers, sponsors and online stores that sell a variety of goods and services. These vendors may ask you for information, such as your name and credit card number. iAfrica.com does _not_ collect, use or disclose this information, nor does it own or control the vendors or have responsibility for transactions made by those merchants. If you would like to know more about the information collected when you participate in e-commerce through this site, please contact the merchants directly.

## Cookies

A “cookie” is a small data text file that can be placed in your browser to enable a server to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies are necessary for this and other sites to provide individualized services, such as subscriptions.

Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, nor does iAfrica.com use cookies to collect personal information. In addition to recognizing subscribers, our cookies may sometimes be used to track which parts of our site you have used so that we can better serve you when you return. Advertisers may use cookies to determine or control how many times you see their message or to customize the message you are presented.

## Email

iAfrica.com will _never_ give your email address to anyone else. We will only send you mail in response to your questions, as follow-up to your transactions, or as part of services for which you have signed up.

## Disclosing Information to Others

iAfrica.com will only disclose personal information when required to do so by law or when we have your explicit permission to do so.
